question_data = [
    {"text": "A slug's blood is green.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "answer": "True"},
    { "text": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, you are free to take it home "
              "to eat.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled to a state funeral.",
     "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "answer": "True"},
    {"text": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "answer": "False"},
    {"text": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "answer": "True"}
]

# question_data = [
#         {
#             "category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
#             "question": "In Norse mythology, Thor once dressed as a woman.",
#             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
#         },
#         {
#             "category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
#             "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Zeus can control lightning.",
#             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
#         },
#         {
#             "category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
#             "question": "According to Norse mythology, Loki is a mother.",
#             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
#         },
#         {
#             "category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
#             "question": "The Japanese god Izanagi successfully returned his wife Izanami from the Underworld.",
#             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
#         },
#         {
#             "category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
#             "question": "Rannamaari was a sea demon that haunted the people of the Maldives and had to be appeased "
#                         "monthly with the sacrifice of a virgin girl.",
#             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
#         },
#         {
#             "category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
#             "question": "In Greek mythology, Hera is the goddess of harvest.",
#             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
#         },
#         {
#             "category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
#             "question": "According to Greek Mythology, Atlas was an Olympian God.",
#             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
#         },
#         {
#             "category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
#             "question": "The Roman god &quot;Jupiter&quot; was first known as &quot;Zeus&quot; to the Greeks.",
#             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
#         },
#         {
#             "category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy",
#             "question": "A wyvern is the same as a dragon.",
#             "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
#         },
#         {
#             "category": "Mythology", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard",
#             "question": "Janus was the Roman god of doorways and passageways.",
#             "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]
#         }
#     ]
